<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TEMPLATE</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on TEMPLATE</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-au</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>01: intro</title><link>/week01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week01/</guid><description>week01 COMP6443 Thanks Lachlan+Andrew for some of the slides
Good faith policy We expect a high standard of professionalism from you at all times while you are taking any of our courses. We expect all students to act in good faith at all times
TLDR: Don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick
sec.edu.au/good-faith-policy
&amp;gt; whoami George Muscat 4th Year CS (Security) how to contact me Email: g.muscat@unsw.edu.au &amp;lt;&amp;ndash; Official Stuff Teams: George Muscat &amp;lt;&amp;ndash; Quicker Official Stuff @woop.</description></item><item><title>02: Auth[ZN]</title><link>/week02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week02/</guid><description>week02 COMP6443 Thanks Lachlan+Andrew for some of the slides
Good Faith Policy We expect a high standard of professionalism from you at all times while you are taking any of our courses. We expect all students to act in good faith at all times.
TLDR: Don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick
sec.edu.au/good-faith-policy
Admin Challenges WebCMS3 Create report groups (will do later) Correction: Points to not necessarily indicate difficulty Challenges Flags for approximately a CR Sales flag 3 Blogs Files Support Due Sunday 3/3 Content HTTP + TLS Status Codes Authentication Sessions Tokens (JWT, Flask, Express etc) Cookies Authorization Permission control IDOR Authentication Verifying that your identity is authentic Factors of authentication are something you Know (e.</description></item><item><title>03: Auth &amp; Trust</title><link>/week03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week03/</guid><description>Week03 Feedback less/same/more yapping?
Report Key things:
Report Groups Format Due date + submission Important Parts LINKED TABLE OF CONTENTS Linked appendix for: verbose definitions screenshots code long payloads Should address vulnerability, not flag Memes only outside of content Lectures This is the law, watch.
Examples Professional Andrew Content PKI Certificates Trust HSTS Authentication MFA TOTP SSO + OAuth + SAML (Extended) Secrets PKI Public Key Infrastructure
Used to determine who is/owns something Uses Certificates Based on trust Certificates TLS (and mTLS) Handshake Certificate Authorities (CA) CA issues certs CAs sign certs with their root cert Root certs are stored in OS/Browsers Trust HSTS HTTP Strict Transport Security</description></item><item><title>04: Injection (pt 1)</title><link>/week04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week04/</guid><description>Week04 Thanks Lachlan and Andrew for some content
Review Any questions about previous content?
Content Injection SQLi SSTI SSRF Injection Injection attacks occur when an attacker injects malicious data that is then used to control program behaviour
SQL Structured Query Language
Language for querying databases Implementations include: PostgreSQL MySQL SQLite SQL Server (Microsoft) SQL Statements SELECT _ FROM _ &amp;hellip; INSERT INTO _ (COLn, &amp;hellip;) VALUES (VALn, &amp;hellip;) UPDATE _ SET _ = _ &amp;hellip; DELETE FROM _ &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; &amp;ndash; this is a comment &amp;hellip; # this can also be a comment (sometimes) … SQL Syntax WHERE</description></item><item><title>07: Client Side Injection</title><link>/week07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/week07/</guid><description>week07 COMP6443 Thanks Lachlan+Andrew for some of the slides
Good Faith Policy We expect a high standard of professionalism from you at all times while you are taking any of our courses. We expect all students to act in good faith at all times.
TLDR: Don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick
sec.edu.au/good-faith-policy
Questions? Client Side Injection WWW Everything is a document Origin vs Site HTML + JS DOM XSS Source + Sink Goals Exfiltration Methods CSRF WAF Bypass Encoding Other tricks Prevention CORS SOP CSP WWW World Wide Web Everything is a document How those documents is client dependent HTML, JS, VBScript DOM Document Object Model An API for scripting languages to interact with web documents document.</description></item></channel></rss>